<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Foodies</string>
    <string name="adobo">

        •	1 1/2 lbs chicken cut into pieces\n\n
•	1 cup coconut vinegar\n\n
•	1 piece Knorr Chicken Cube\n\n
•	1 1/2 cups water\n\n
•	1 teaspoon crushed pepper\n\n
•	5 cloves garlic\n\n
•	1 teaspoon sugar\n\n
•	4 pieces dried bay leaves\n\n
•	4 tablespoons cooking oil\n


    </string>
    <string name="adobocook">

1.	Arrange chicken in a large bowl. Add black pepper, garlic, and coconut vinegar. Mix well. Marinate for at least 30 minutes.\n\n
2.	Separate the marinade ingredients from the chicken. Heat oil in a pan. Fry each chicken piece for 1 ½ minutes per side. Remove from the pan, and then place on a clean plate. Set aside.\n\n
3.	Using the remaining oil, saute garlic for 20 seconds. Add the pan-fried chicken. Pour the remaining marinade ingredients and add water. Let boil.\n\n
4.	Add Knorr Chicken Cube and bay leaves. Cover the pan and adjust heat between low and medium. Cook for 20 minutes. Add more water if needed.\n\n
5.	Flip the chicken using a pair of kitchen tongs. Season with sugar and salt as needed. Cook for 5 minutes.\n\n
6.	Transfer to a serving plate. Serve with warm rice. Share and enjoy!


    </string>
    <string name="caldereta">

        •	2 lbs chicken cut into pieces\n\n
•	1 piece Knorr Chicken Cube\n\n
•	2 pieces carrots wedged\n\n
•	2 pieces potato cubed\n\n
•	8 ounces tomato sauce\n\n
•	2 pieces bell pepper sliced\n\n
•	4 tablespoons liver spread\n\n
•	1 piece tomato cubed\n\n
•	3 pieces chili pepper chopped\n\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n\n
•	3 cloves garlic crushed\n\n
•	3 tablespoons cheddar cheese grated\n\n
•	1 ½ cups water\n\n
•	4 tablespoons cooking oil\n\n


    </string>

    <string name="calderetains">
        1.	Start by pan-frying the potato and carrots. Heat oil in a pan. Add potato. Fry each side for 1 minute. Remove from the pan and put in a bowl lined with paper towel. Set aside. Do the same thing with the carrots.\n\n
2.	Using the remaining oil, fry the chicken for 1 ½ minutes per side. Remove from the pan. Set aside.\n\n
3.	Saute onion and garlic. Add tomato. Continue to saute while stirring until tomato and onion softens.\n\n
4.	Add chicken and pour-in tomato sauce and water. Let boil.\n\n
5.	Stir and then add Knorr Chicken Cube and chili pepper. Cover the pan. Cook between low to medium heat for 15 minutes.\n\n
6.	Turn the chicken pieces over to equally cook the opposite side. Add liver spread. Stir. Cover and cook for 20 minutes.\n\n
7.	Add bell peppers and cheese. Cook for 3 minutes.\n\n
8.	Put the carrots and potatoes into the pan. Continue to cook for 5 to 7 minutes.\n\n
9.	Season with salt and ground black pepper. Serve. Share and enjoy.

    </string>
    <string name="lollipop">

•	10 pieces chicken wings\n\n
•	1 1/2 cup Panko bread crumbs\n\n
•	2 pieces raw eggs\n\n
•	1/2 cup all-purpose flour\n\n
•	3 teaspoons salt\n\n
•	1/2 teaspoon ground black pepper\n\n
•	2 cups cooking oil\n\n


</string>
    <string name="lollipopins">

1.	Divide the chicken wing into 3 parts by slicing through the joints. Set aside the wingtip for other possible uses.\n\n
2.	Shape the wing to look like a lollipop. You should have two parts of the chicken wing by now: the one with a single bone and the one with two bones. Start by selecting the part with one bone.\n\n
3.	Separate the meat from the bone by sliding a sharp knife around the tip of the bone where meat is still connected (do not cut through the bone).\n\n
4.	Place the wing vertically on top of a flat surface while holding the part where the knife passed.\n\n
5.	Gently push downward while gripping the bone with your thumb and index finger until the meat slides down.\n\n
6.	Arrange the meat by inverting the inner part until a lollipop shape is formed. Note: Do the same procedure for the part with two bones. However, you need to first detach the smaller bone before commencing.\n\n
7.	Season the chicken lollipops with salt and pepper and let it stand for at least 15 minutes.\n\n
8.	Crack the eggs and transfer to a bowl then whisk.\n\n
9.	Gradually add-in the all-purpose flour while whisking until a batter is formed.\n\n
10.	Dip the chicken lollipop on the batter then to the Panko breadcrumbs.\n\n
11.	Heat oil in a cooking pot then deep-fry the chicken lollipop under medium heat until the color of the outer part turns medium brown (about 10 to 12 minutes).\n\n
12.	Remove the fried chicken lollipop from the cooking pot and transfer to a dish with paper towel. Let it stand until excess oil is absorbed by the paper towel.\n\n
13.	Serve with your favorite dip. Share and enjoy!



    </string>
    <string name="parmesan">

•	1 lb. chicken breast boneless\n\n
•	28 g Knorr SavorRich Chicken\n\n
•	1 ½ cups fresh mushroom sliced\n\n
•	½ cup Parmesan cheese grated\n\n
•	4 cloves garlic minced\n\n
•	3 tablespoons all-purpose flour\n\n
•	2 ½ cups milk\n\n
•	3 tablespoons butter\n\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n\n
•	Ground black pepper to taste



</string>
    <string name="parmesanins">
        1.	Slice the boneless chicken breast into thin pieces. Brush Knorr savorRich chicken seasoning all over the chicken. Let it stay for 15 minutes.\n\n
2.	Heat oil in a pan. Fry the chicken for 4 1.2 minutes per side. Transfer the chicken to a plate afterwards. Set aside.\n\n
3.	Start to make the creamy sauce by melting butter on the same pan the chicken was cooked. Saute mushrooms for 2 minutes. Add garlic and continue to cook for 30 seconds.\n\n
4.	Gradually add all-purpose flour. Continuously stir until lumps form.\n\n
5.	Slowly pour around ¾ of the total milk amount. Stir until the cream sauce becomes smooth. Add Parmesan cheese. Stir.\n\n
6.	Pour remaining milk while stirring. Season with ground black pepper.\n\n
7.	Put the chicken back into the pan. Cover and cook between low to medium heat for 3 minutes.\n\n
8.	Transfer to a serving plate. Serve with your favorite side\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="soup">

•	1 lb. chicken breast\n\n
•	1 piece Knorr Chicken Cube\n\n
•	10 pieces asparagus cut into pieces\n\n
•	1 ½ cups spinach\n\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n\n
•	4 cloves garlic chopped\n\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n\n
•	2 quarts water\n\n
•	Salt and ground black pepper to taste\n\n




</string>
    <string name="soupins">


1.	Boil water in a cooking pot. Add chicken. Cover and boil for 20 minutes. Remove chicken and let it cool down. Shred the meat and set aside. Save the chicken stock.\n\n
2.	Heat oil in a cooking pot. Sauté onion and garlic until onion softens.\n\n
3.	Add chicken. Sauté for 1 minute.\n\n
4.	Pour-in chicken stock. Let boil.\n\n
5.	Add Knorr Chicken Cube. Stir. Cover and cook for 5 minutes.\n\n
6.	Add asparagus. Cook for 5 minutes.\n\n
7.	Add spinach and season with salt and ground black pepper.\n\n
8.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve.


    </string>

    <string name="fried">

        •	1 ½ lbs. chicken drumsticks\n\n
•	16 ml Knorr SavorRich Chicken Liquid Seasoning\n\n
•	½ cup all-purpose flour\n\n
•	5 tablespoons soy sauce\n\n
•	2 pieces calamansi\n\n
•	1/8 teaspoon ground black pepper\n\n
•	2 cups cooking oil\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="friedins">

        1.	Create slits on the chicken drumsticks by slicing all the way to the bone.\n\n
2.	Place the chicken inside a resealable bag. Add soy sauce, calamansi juice, Knorr SavorRich, and ground black pepper. Seal the bag and then shake until all ingredients are well blended. Push the air out of the bag and seal again. Marinate for 10 minutes.\n\n
3.	Heat oil in a pot.\n\n
4.	Place the flour in a container with cover. Put the marinated chicken in the container (one to two pieces at a time). Cover and shake until the chicken get completely coated with flour. Shake-off excess flour.\n\n
5.	Deep-fry the chicken for 14 minutes.\n\n
6.	Remove from the pot and let the chicken rest for 5 minutes.\n\n
7.	Serve with rice or any of your favorite side dishes.

    </string>
    <string name="ginataan">
        •	1 lb chicken cut into serving pieces\n\n
•	1 piece green papaya small, sliced into wedges\n\n
•	1 cups spinach\n\n
•	2 cups coconut milk\n\n
•	6 pieces chili pepper\n\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n\n
•	4 cloves garlic minced\n\n
•	2 thumbs ginger julienne\n\n
•	Patis and ground black pepper to taste\n\n
•	4 tablespoons cooking oil\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="ginataanins">
        1.	Heat oil in a cooking pot.\n\n
2.	Pan-fry chicken for 1 1/2 minutes per side. Remove from the pot. Set aside.\n\n
3.	Saute onion, ginger, and garlic in the remaining oil until onion softens.\n\n
4.	Put- the pan-fried chicken into the pot. Cook for 1 minute.\n\n
5.	Pour coconut milk into the pan. Let boil.\n\n
6.	Add chili pepper. Cover the pan and adjust heat between low to medium. Cook for 30 minutes or until the chicken becomes tender.\n\n
7.	Add papaya. Stir. Cook for 5 minutes.\n\n
8.	Put the spinach into the pot. Cook for 2 minutes.\n\n
9.	Season with patis and ground black pepper.\n\n
10.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve. Share and enjoy\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="bicol">
        •	1 lb. boneless chicken breast sliced\n\n
•	1 piece Knorr Chicken Cube\n\n
•	2 cups coconut milk\n\n
•	2 pieces long green pepper sliced\n\n
•	5 pieces Thai chili pepper chopped\n\n
•	1 thumb ginger minced\n\n
•	1 tablespoon bagoong alamang\n\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n\n
•	4 cloves garlic crushed\n\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="bicolins">
1.	Heat oil in a cooking pot. Saute garlic, onion, and ginger.\n\n
2.	Once the onion softens, add chicken and chili peppers. Stir and cook until chicken turns light brown.\n\n
3.	Pour-in coconut milk. Let boil.\n\n
4.	Add Knorr Chicken Cube. Continue to cook between low to medium heat until the coconut milk reduces to half.\n\n
5.	Add bagoong alamang and log green peppers. Cover and cook for 2 minutes.\n\n
6.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve!\n\n
7.	Share and enjoy


    </string>
    <string name="adobomanok">

        •	2 lbs chicken sliced into serving pieces\n\n
•	1 piece Knorr Chicken Cube\n\n
•	1 head garlic crushed\n\n
•	3/4 cup white vinegar\n\n
•	6 tablespoons soy sauce\n\n
•	1 1/2 teaspoons whole peppercorn\n\n
•	5 pieces dried bay leaves\n\n
•	1/2 cup water\n\n
•	1 teaspoon sugar\n\n
•	4 tablespoons cooking oil\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="adobomanokins">

        1.	Combine chicken, 1/4 of the total amount of garlic, whole peppercorn, dried bay leaves, soy sauce, vinegar, and water in a cooking pot. Cover and let boil. Stir and make sure that all ingredients are well blended.\n\n
2.	Add Knorr Chicken Cube and sugar. Stir. Cover the pot and cook for 10 minutes.\n\n
3.	Turn the chicken over and cook the opposite side for another 10 minutes. Set aside.\n\n
4.	Heat oil in a clean pan. Saute remaining garlic until it turns light brown.\n\n
5.	Pan fry the chicken for 1 minute per side. Pour the adobo sauce into the pan. Boil until it reduces to half.\n\n
6.	Transfer to a serving plate. Serve with warm rice

    </string>

    <string name="pastel">
        •	2 lbs chicken breast cut into cubes\n\n
•	1 piece Knorr Chicken Cube\n\n
•	1 piece Chorizo de Bilbao sliced\n\n
•	4 pieces hotdogs sliced\n\n
•	1 piece potato cubed\n\n
•	1 piece carrot sliced\n\n
•	1 piece red bell pepper sliced\n\n
•	1 piece green bell pepper sliced\n\n
•	3/4 cup button mushroom sliced\n\n
•	15 ounces all-purpose cream\n\n
•	1/4 cup soy sauce\n\n
•	1 piece lime\n\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n\n
•	4 cloves garlic minced\n\n
•	3/4 cup water\n\n
•	Salt and ground black pepper to taste

    </string>
    <string name="pastelins">

1.	Combine chicken, soy sauce, and lime in a large bowl. Mix well. Marinate chicken for at least 30 minutes.\n\n
2.	Heat oil in a cooking pot. Saute onion and garlic.\n\n
3.	Once the onion softens, add the chorizo. Saute for 1 minute.\n\n
4.	Put chicken into the pot. Saute until the color turns light brown.\n\n
5.	Add water. Let boil.\n\n
6.	Add Knorr Chicken Cube. Stir. Cover and continue to cook for 20 minutes.\n\n
7.	Put the sliced hotdogs into the pot. Cook in medium heat until the liquid reduces to half.\n\n
8.	Add potato and carrot. Pour-in all-purpose cream. Cover and cook for 8 minutes.\n\n
9.	Stir-in the mushroom and bell peppers. Stir. Cook for 3 minutes.\n\n
10.	Season with ground black pepper and salt.\n\n
11.	Transfer to a serving plate. Serve with warm rice. Share and enjoy.



    </string>
    <string name="SINANGLAY">
    •	2 pieces tilapia cleaned and scales removed\n\n
    •	4 pieces bok choy or pechay leaves\n\n
    •	4 cloves garlic chopped\n\n
    •	1 piece onion diced\n\n
    •	2 pieces tomato diced\n\n
    •	1 thumb ginger chopped\n\n
    •	3 pieces long green chili\n\n
    •	1 1/2 cups coconut milk\n\n
    •	1/2 cup water\n\n
        •	1 teaspoon salt
    </string>
    <string name="sinanglayins">
        1.	In a bowl, combine garlic, onion, tomatoes, and ginger then mix.\n\n
2.	Stuff the tilapia with the garlic, onion, and ginger mixture.\n\n
3.	Wrap the bok choy around the tilapia. I use 2 bok choy leaves to ensure that the entire fish is wrapped.\n\n
4.	Secure the bok choy by tying a kitchen twine around the tilapia. (this step is optional)\n\n
5.	Arrange the wrapped tilapia in a wide cooking pan then pour-in coconut milk and water. Sprinkle salt, cover, and turn on heat.\n\n
6.	Cook the fish in medium heat for 20 minutes.\n\n
7.	Turn off heat. Remove the cooking twine and transfer the fish to a serving plate.\n\n
8.	Serve hot. Share and enjoy!

    </string>
</resources>
